Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 5: Boxes 257-319
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 5: Boxes 257-319
- United Public Workers of America (UPW), Publication (Box 308, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: An analysis of 113 photostats presented in "evidence" to the CIO Trail Committee, January 9, 1950, at the U.P.W. hearing, Publication (Box 308, Folder 8)
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 309, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Paper unions fight rise in mail rates, 1950-1955 (Box 309, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Earl Radliff retains Presidency, 1950-1955 (Box 309, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Quebec unions decertified for illegal strikes, 1950-1955 (Box 309, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Sulphite strike opposed, 1950-1955 (Box 309, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: John P. Burke, International Head, Pulp, Sulphite, paper Mill Union aids in ending threat of strike, 1950-1955 (Box 309, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Struck paper mills are closed by owner, 1950-1955 (Box 309, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: The Group insurance plan of the International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers of the United States and Canada., Publication (Box 309, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: The Group insurance plan of the Central Pennsylvania Pipe Trades Health and Welfare Plan, Publication (Box 309, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Pension plan: International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers Pension Fund, Publication (Box 309, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Benefits through the Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Union and Industry National Pension Plan, 1962; Publication (Box 309, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Paper industry union-management pension fund, 1971; Publication (Box 309, Folder 1)
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 309, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report of the International Executive Board to the delegates of the ... Convention of the International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, 1947; Publication (Box 309, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Report of the International Executive Board to the delegates of the ... Convention of the International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, 1950; Publication (Box 309, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Report of the International Executive Board to the delegates of the ... Convention of the International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, 1956; Publication (Box 309, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Report of the International Executive Board to the delegates of the ... Convention of the International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, 1959; Publication (Box 309, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Report of the International Executive Board to the delegates of the ... Convention of the International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, 1971; Publication (Box 309, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Report of the Unity Committee, 1956; Publication (Box 309, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Minutes of the meetin of the International Executive Board., 1943; Publication (Box 309, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Minutes of the meetin of the International Executive Board., 1955; Publication (Box 309, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Minutes of the meetin of the International Executive Board., 1956; Publication (Box 309, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Minutes of the meetin of the International Executive Board., 1957; Publication (Box 309, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Minutes of the meetin of the International Executive Board., 1963; Publication (Box 309, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Minutes of the meetin of the International Executive Board., 1964; Publication (Box 309, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Introducing your union, 1954; Publication (Box 309, Folder 2)
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 309, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Introducing your union, 1960; Publication (Box 309, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: A contemporary analysis of a labor union, 1961; Publication (Box 309, Folder 3)
    Author: Miles E. Hoffman
  - Item 3: Instructions for use of revised financial forms, 1948; Publication (Box 309, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: What is your union? A booklet for new members, 1945; Publication (Box 309, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Local union administration, Publication (Box 309, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: A prospectus for the 1970's adopted by the International Executive Board.at its summer session, June 8, 1971., Publication (Box 309, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Project III, an environmental program for local unions, 1971; Publication (Box 309, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Project III, occupational safety and health, 1971; Publication (Box 309, Folder 3)
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 309, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Report of the Research and Education Dept.26th International Convention, 1962; Publication (Box 309, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Instructions for use of revised financial forms, 1946; Publication (Box 309, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Tips for local union education programs, 1953; Publication (Box 309, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Selected clauses in collective bargaining agreements in the pulp and paper industry related to automation and technological change, 1964; Publication (Box 309, Folder 4)
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 309, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Financial report, 1961-1965 (Box 309, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Financial report, 1966; Publication (Box 309, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Financial report, 1968-1969 (Box 309, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Financial report, 1971; Publication (Box 309, Folder 5)
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 309, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Champion: A historic meeting by Louis Gordon, 1956-1957 (Box 309, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Champion, 1948; Publication (Box 309, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 3, no. 2 (1948)
  - Item 3: Champion, 1949; Publication (Box 309, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 4, no. 3 (1949)
  - Item 4: Champion, 1950; Publication (Box 309, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 5, no.1 (1950)
  - Item 5: Champion, 1951; Publication (Box 309, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 7, no. 4 (1951)
  - Item 6: Champion, 1952; Publication (Box 309, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 8, no. 3-4 (1952)
  - Item 7: Champion, 1952; Publication (Box 309, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 9, no. 6 (1952)
  - Item 8: Champion, 1953; Publication (Box 309, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 10, no. 1 (1953)
  - Item 9: Champion, 1953; Publication (Box 309, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. II, no. 3, 5 (1953)
  - Item 10: Champion, 1954; Publication (Box 309, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. III, no.1-3 (1954)
  - Item 11: Champion, 1955; Publication (Box 309, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. VIII, no.5-8 (1955)
  - Item 12: Boxmaster 381, 1948; Publication (Box 309, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 1, no. 3-5 (1948)
  - Item 13: Local 107 News, 1955; Publication (Box 309, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 8, no. 9 (1955)
  - Item 14: Local 107 News, 1956; Publication (Box 309, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 9, no. 1-2 (1956)
  - Item 15: Medical Specialist Service, 1953; Publication (Box 309, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: The health & welfare fund for Local 299, 1949; Publication (Box 309, Folder 6)
  - Item 17: Your group insurance plan, 1947; Publication (Box 309, Folder 6)
    Author: International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers. Folding Box & Display Workers Union. Local 381
  - Item 18: The Welfare fund plan of the Local Union No. 413, 1951; Publication (Box 309, Folder 6)
    Author: International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers. Local 413
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 309, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Graphic Arts IndustryPreparing for today's and tomorrow's rapidly changing technology, Publication (Box 309, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: News Letter from the International Office, 1955-1956 (Box 309, Folder 7)
    Notes: no. 7-8 (1955)
  - Item 3: News Letter from the International Office, 1955-1956 (Box 309, Folder 7)
    Notes: no. 2, 4-6 (1956)
  - Item 4: News Letter from the International Office, 1950; Publication (Box 309, Folder 7)
    Notes: no. 1 (1950)
  - Item 5: News Letter from the International Office, 1951; Publication (Box 309, Folder 7)
    Notes: no. 4, 6-7 (1951)
  - Item 6: News Letter from the International Office, 1952; Publication (Box 309, Folder 7)
    Notes: no. 1 (1952)
  - Item 7: News Letter from the International Office, 1953; Publication (Box 309, Folder 7)
    Notes: no. 10 (1953)
  - Item 8: News Letter from the International Office, 1954; Publication (Box 309, Folder 7)
    Notes: no. 1, 3-5, 7-8 (1954)
  - Item 9: News Letter from the International Office, 1955; Publication (Box 309, Folder 7)
    Notes: no. 2-6 (1955)
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 310, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Correspondence, 1955; Publication (Box 310, Folder 1)
    Author: International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers
  - Item 2: Statement on Amalgamation made by John P. Burke, President-Secretary., 1955; Publication (Box 310, Folder 1)
    Author: John P. Burke
  - Item 3: Labor Day address by John P. Burke, 1948; Publication (Box 310, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: article - Union training program of the AFL paper unions by George W. Brooks and Russell Allen, 1952; Publication (Box 310, Folder 1)
    Author: George W. Brooks; Allen Russell
  - Item 5: The old pay check goes on by John P Burke, 1945; Publication (Box 310, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: A report form Representative Charles E. Stewart on the 1954 Christmas Party, Publication (Box 310, Folder 1)
    Author: Charles E. Stewart
  - Item 7: Minutes of the meeting of the Joint Boards of the., 1951; Publication (Box 310, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Editorials by John P. Burke, 1954-1955 (Box 310, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Articles by John P. Burke, 1950-1955 (Box 310, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Address delivered on October 6 and 7 by Int'l. Rep. Charles E. Stewart, 1953; Publication (Box 310, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Do's and don'ts for Shop Stewards and Standing Committees, 1945; Publication (Box 310, Folder 1)
    Author: John Sherman
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 310, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: A union's steward-training program, 1951; Publication (Box 310, Folder 2)
    Author: George W. Brooks; Sara Gamm
    Notes: Reprinted from ILR Review, vol. 4, no. 2 Jan. 1951
  - Item 2: Address; Report, 1933-1941 (Box 310, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Resolutions presented by locals of the., 1941-1947 (Box 310, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Economic democracy in pulp and paper, 1948; Publication (Box 310, Folder 2)
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 310, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Report of Committee on rules and order of business, Publication (Box 310, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Adresses. From Twenty-ninth convention., 1971; Publication (Box 310, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Roll call of Delegates to the twent-sixth convention, 1962; Publication (Box 310, Folder 3)
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 310, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Address delivered March 7, 1957, Publication (Box 310, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Training material, 1959; Publication (Box 310, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Special Convention, 1972; Publication (Box 310, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Agreement for merger as adopted by the International Executive Boards of and the United Papermakers and Paperworkers, 1972; Publication (Box 310, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Agreement for merger as adopted by the International Executive Boards of and the United Papermakers and PaperworkersAttachment C, 1972; Publication (Box 310, Folder 4)
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 310, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: How to conduct a union meeting., Publication (Box 310, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Do's and don'ts for Shop Stewards and Standing Committees, 1958; Publication (Box 310, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Attachment B -- Constitution, 1969; Publication (Box 310, Folder 5)
    Author: United Papermakers and Paperworkers
  - Item 4: Attachment A -- 1971 Constitution and Bylaws, Publication (Box 310, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: A contemporary analysis of a labor union, 1961; Publication (Box 310, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Introducing your union ..., 1957; Publication (Box 310, Folder 5)
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 310, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Resolutions presented to the twenty-eighth convention of the International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers: Diplomat Hotel-Hollywood, Florida, October 7-12, 1968, Publication (Box 310, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Report of zone conference, Jacksonville, Florida, October 26, 27, 28, 1945, Publication (Box 310, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Report of zone conference, Mobile, Alabama, Cawthon Hotel, February 1, 2 and 3, 1946, Monroe, Louisiana, Labor Temple, February 5, 6 and 7, 1946, Publication (Box 310, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Mid-Year Economic Report on the Pulp and Paper Industry, 1971; Publication (Box 310, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Economic report pulp and paper industry, 1955; Publication (Box 310, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: 26th International Convention, 1962; Publication (Box 310, Folder 6)
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 310, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Introducing your union, 1954; Publication (Box 310, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Resolutions presented to the twenty-sixth convention of the International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers: Cobo Hall-Detroit, Michigan, September 10-15, 1962, Publication (Box 310, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Resolutions presented to the twenty-fourth convention of the International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers: Milwaukee Auditorium, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, September 24- 29, 1956, Publication (Box 310, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Design for Progress '65, 1965; Publication (Box 310, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Report, 1933; Publication (Box 310, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Pollution take a stand, Publication (Box 310, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Resolutions presented by locals of the., 1941; Publication (Box 310, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Supplement to 1958 Economic ReportWage differentials, Publication (Box 310, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Permanent Committees of the twenty-sixth convention, 1962; Publication (Box 310, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Permanent Committees of the twenty-eighth convention, 1968; Publication (Box 310, Folder 7)
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 310, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Research and Education Bulletin, 1945; Publication (Box 310, Folder 8)
    Notes: no. 1-3 (1945- 1946)
  - Item 2: Research and Education Bulletin, 1946; Publication (Box 310, Folder 8)
    Notes: Special issue no. 1-2 (1946)
  - Item 3: Research and Education Bulletin, 1946; Publication (Box 310, Folder 8)
    Notes: West Coast issue no. 1 (1946)
- American Radio Association (ARA), Publication (Box 311, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 311, Folder 1)
    Author: American Radio Association
  - Item 2: Negotiating Committee Report, 1948; Publication (Box 311, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Radio Newscast, 1948; Publication (Box 311, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Marine Journal: A periodical of interpretation, 1950; Publication (Box 311, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol. 77, no.4 (1950)
  - Item 5: Preamble, 1955; Publication (Box 311, Folder 1)
    Author: Mystic Steamship Division
  - Item 6: National Assignment rules, 1954; Publication (Box 311, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: ARA-PMA welfare plan, 1954; Publication (Box 311, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: then and now ARA faces the 60's, 1960; Publication (Box 311, Folder 1)
- American Radio Association (ARA), Publication (Box 311, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Settlement of Directors guild contract row expected, removing strike threat, 1950; Publication (Box 311, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Re: FCC Docket 9240, Brief submitted, Publication (Box 311, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Re: FCC Docket 9387, Brief submitted, Publication (Box 311, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Re: FCC Docket 8913, Brief submitted, Publication (Box 311, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: In the matter of the arbitration between Committee for Companies and Agents, Atlantic and Gulf Coasts (Radio Officers) and American Radio Association, 1949; Publication (Box 311, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: ARA welfare plans, 1972; Publication (Box 311, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Railroad Employees Incorporated, Publication (Box 311, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Correspondence, 1968; Publication (Box 311, Folder 3)
    Author: Railway Labor Executives' Association
  - Item 2: Recession medicine: Higher spending or lower taxes?, Publication (Box 311, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Communications Journal, 1937; Publication (Box 311, Folder 3)
    Author: American Radio Telegraphists Assn.
    Notes: vol. 1, no. 11-12 (1937)
  - Item 4: Amalgamated Railroad Employees Incorporated, Publication (Box 311, Folder 3)
- United Railroad Operating Crafts (UROC), Publication (Box 311, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Correspondence, 1951; Publication (Box 311, Folder 4)
    Author: United Railroad Operating Crafts
  - Item 2: Minutes, 1956; Publication (Box 311, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Resolutions and Amendments for referendum vote, 1958; Publication (Box 311, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Public Law 914 - 81st Congress, 1951; Publication (Box 311, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: The origin, activities, and purposes of the railroad labor unions, 1957; Publication (Box 311, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: An outline and recommendation for handling grievances, 1956; Publication (Box 311, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: A program for the men of the C.J., 1952; Publication (Box 311, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Union shop vs. human rights, Publication (Box 311, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Report of Chief Exec. Of Fifteen cooperating railway labor organizations participating in the Joint National Rules Movement, 1953; Publication (Box 311, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: The Supreme Council of the United Order of Railway Employees, Publication (Box 311, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: The case for one union for all Railroad Employees, Publication (Box 311, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Parliamentary procedure and proper conduct at meetings, Publication (Box 311, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Unite Now!, Publication (Box 311, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Read the following for legal proof of your right to choose your own representative, Publication (Box 311, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Dispute between the railway carriers and four operating, 1951; Publication (Box 311, Folder 4)
    Author: United States. Congress. Senate. Committee on Labor and Public Welfare
  - Item 16: Operating Brotherhoods speakers union, 1959; Publication (Box 311, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: You and UROC: a brochure of information for the railroad crafts!, Publication (Box 311, Folder 4)
    Author: Unite Railroad Operating Crafts
  - Item 18: U.R.O.C.: outline for handling grievances and investigations, 1953; Publication (Box 311, Folder 4)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America, Publication (Box 312, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Amendments to the constitution of the Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America, 1953; Publication (Box 312, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: 50 years of railroad signaling: a history of the Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America., 1951; Publication (Box 312, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America, Publication (Box 312, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen Wage notice, 1981; Publication (Box 312, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Memorandum of the Interstate commerce act, 1961; Publication (Box 312, Folder 2)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America, Publication (Box 312, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Tough Chief Signalman.by Richard Halloran, 1971; Publication (Box 312, Folder 3)
    Author: Richard Halloran
  - Item 2: Radio Address, 1928; Publication (Box 312, Folder 3)
    Author: Leonard Jackson Ross
  - Item 3: Minutes of the Ninth Annual and Eleventh Regular Convention of the Brotherhood Railroad Signalmen of America, 1916; Publication (Box 312, Folder 3)
- Order of Railroad Telegraphers (U.S.), Publication (Box 312, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Order of Railroad Telegraphersproposed amendments and resolutions - Book no. 1, Book no. 2, 1964; Publication (Box 312, Folder 4)
    Author: Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America
  - Item 2: Court backs move of US mediators, 1949; Publication (Box 312, Folder 4)
- Order of Railroad Telegraphers (U.S.), Publication (Box 312, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Statement of G. E. Leighty to Special Subcommittee of the Senate Committee on the Judiciary on S.3548, 1960; Publication (Box 312, Folder 5)
    Author: G. E. Leighty
  - Item 2: Official Directory of Grand Division and Subordinate Div. the Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1946; Publication (Box 312, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Official Directory of The Order of Railroad Telegraphers, Grand Division and Subordinate Division, 1950; Publication (Box 312, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Official Directory of The Order of Railroad Telegraphers, Grand Division and Subordinate Division, 1952; Publication (Box 312, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Official Directory of The Order of Railroad Telegraphers, Grand Division and Subordinate Division, 1954; Publication (Box 312, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Official Directory of The Order of Railroad Telegraphers, Grand Division and Subordinate Division, 1956; Publication (Box 312, Folder 5)
- Order of Railroad Telegraphers (U.S.), Publication (Box 312, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Schedules and wage scales in effect December 31, 1917, 1918; Publication (Box 312, Folder 6)
- Order of Railroad Telegraphers (U.S.), Publication (Box 312, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Report of Finance Committee to the Thirty-Sixth Regular and Third Quadrennial Session of the Grand Division, 1964; Publication (Box 312, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Temporary Roll.36th Regular and 3rd Quadrennial session of the Grand Division, 1964; Publication (Box 312, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Laws affecting railroad telegraphers in the United States and Canada., 1909; Publication (Box 312, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Minutes of meeting of National Schedule Committee of the Order of Railroad Telegraphers: held at Saint Louis, Missouri, September 1st to 9th, 1919, Publication (Box 312, Folder 7)
    Author: Order of Railroad Telegraphers (U.S.)
  - Item 5: Report of the Joint Committee representing The Order of Railroad Telegraphers and the Regional Directors to The Board of Railroad Wages and Working Conditions, 1920; Publication (Box 312, Folder 7)
- Non-Operating Railroad Employees, Publication (Box 313, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Basis of agreement, 1951; Publication (Box 313, Folder 1)
    Author: Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (U.S.); Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen; Order of Railway Conductors
  - Item 2: Agreement dated November 1, 1956, between Railroads represented by the Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Conference Committees, Publication (Box 313, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Group hospital, surgical and medical insurance plan, as amended effective December 1, 1956, Publication (Box 313, Folder 1)
    Author: Non-Operating Railroad Employees
  - Item 4: Group hospital, surgical and medical insurance plan, 1955; Publication (Box 313, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Group hospital, surgical and medical insurance plan, covering dependents of active employees, furloughed employees and their dependents, retired employees and their dependents, 1955; Publication (Box 313, Folder 1)
- Non-Operating Railroad Employees, Publication (Box 313, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Agreement dated June 5, 1962 between railroads represented by the Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Conference Committees and the employees of such railroads represented by the Employees' National Conference Committee, Eleven Cooperating Railway, Publication (Box 313, Folder 2)